In light of Racing Girls
running a maid costume event,
we're thinking of doing a
collaboration with a maid café.
Special costumes will be
ordered for the occasion.
For this collaboration, the café interior
will be decorated like the game's world map.
We're looking into three possible locations.
Now, regarding the pricing quotes for
each location, please turn to the next page.
We'll set up a dedicated social media account
for the café. We're aiming for June to...
The last collab café was
a big hit with the customers.
We're very grateful for that.
Their social media went viral
and brought in new fans, too.
I'm so glad to hear that.
We look forward to working with you again.
I'll have you participate in this project, too.
Review and brush up on
the collab café proposal.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Use the plans I made in the past
as a reference to fill in the details.
Ask me if you have any questions.
Yes, ma'am! Thank you very much.
- All right!
- An important part of being a mentor
is creating an atmosphere where the senpai
can feel comfortable lending an ear.
To do that, I need to open
up to Kamegawa more...
Today's the day I invite Kamegawa to lunch!
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
"I Wanna Invite My Junior to Lunch!"
Stare...
Racing Girls!
So you actually play the games
you're in charge of, Senpai.
The clients usually provide the materials,
but I can understand the customers
better if I play them firsthand.
I also like games in general.
Before finalizing your proposal,
do a little test run.
Yes, ma'am!
Ready... go!
Whoa. This is kinda difficult.
I'll demonstrate. Give it here.
Yes, please. Thank you.
To think my gaming skills would
come in handy during his training...
On top of being a loner from gaming too much,
I worked part-time as
a tester during college.
Even now, I just play games
instead of hanging out with others.
Here you go.
Now's the time to show off my skills!
Ready... go!
Huh? It's harder to play than usual!
Oh! It's because I usually play with a controller!
So the controls are a bit...
No, that's no excuse.
Since I told him I'd show him,
I need to stay on course!
As his mentor!
Ow! Huh?!
A-Are you all right?
One more time.
Oh, then... would you like
to practice together?
It has a VS mode, too.
M'kay...
We ended up just sluggishly racing on
a beginner-friendly track together...
The graphics are nice.
Yeah.
This item would be nice to
include in the collab café.
Yeah.
Man, I'm hungry.
Wanna go eat?
Let's go!
Oh, I can't.
Okay.
It's about time I invite Kamegawa to lunch.
M-Maybe it's not the right timing.
Looks like Kamegawa is focused
on something right now.
Excuse me, Kannawa-san?
It's about the app that
Kanzaki-san was in charge of...
Oh, yes.
Excuse me, Senpai...
No problems here. Now you just need
to confirm with the other party—
Kannawa-san. Can I bother you for a bit?
Yes.
- Will you be okay?
- Yes! Thank you so much.
Sorry to bother you when you're busy.
- Wanna eat lunch together, Kamegawa-kun?
- There's something I'd like you to do.
N-No way!
The newbie I'm training is
having his first lunch with...
- About that one sunscreen's PR...
- No, it's good that he's
interacting with the others.
- Can I put you in charge of it after all?
- It's wrong of me to be worried.
- Things got a little out of hand, you see.
- Our model can't fit us in anymore.
- There's this great cheap Italian place nearby.
- There's also family restaurants and ramen.
- We're looking for someone else, but timing's tight.
- I'm sorry. I actually brought my lunch today.
Aw, what bad timing!
We'll invite you some other time.
So, can I entrust this to you, Kannawa-san?
Yes, I understand.
Thanks! Sorry again!
Since it's been bothering me so much...
I need to finally invite him to lunch.
Wait! Since he brought his own,
I can't invite him now, either!
Do I need to invite him in advance?
No. If his mentor says, "We're having
lunch together tomorrow,"
wouldn't that put unnecessary
pressure on him?
What should I do?
BONE BROTH - GOMTANG SOUP
Instant noodles again?!
I-I'm sorry! I'm on a budget...
I'll start saving next month, I promise!
I... I'll treat you!
Huh?
- Let's go.
- I-I can't!
This is my own responsibility and...
What if you show up late
to work due to poor health?
As your mentor, the fault lies with me!
Understand? Now shut up and follow me!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I did it! I finally invited him to lunch!
When I was a newbie,
Kanzaki-senpai often invited me out...
The younger person's supposed to
hand out wet towels and napkins.
Stubborn people will pay
strict attention to that.
Got it!
She told me the ins and outs
of how to be a newbie.
But... even though she'd point
those things out to me,
when we had lunch on our own...
Senpai! That's my job!
Don't worry about it.
You don't need to do those things for me.
Just like Kanzaki-senpai, I, too,
want to be strict when needed,
but not have my junior worry about me.
A smart senpai, just like her...
Here you go, Senpai.
But I wanted to do that for him!
Huh? I-Is something the matter?
Are you ready to order?
I'd like this, please.
Um, and you, Senpai?
Oh, um...
Let's eat—
I told you I'd pay, so you should
eat some meat! Meat!
But I'd feel bad ordering the expensive—
Even so! Who orders just a salad?
Eat meat!
Have! Some!
Meat!
Th-Thank you...
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
I was only thinking about
how to invite him for lunch.
Now that we're here, things ain't right.
Yum!
It's delicious. Thank you.
Sure.
It's been a while since I ate a decent meal.
- Why are you on such a budget?
- Huh?
Should I not have asked?
I can't stick my nose into the
private lives of people at work!
The thing is, well...
there are these... model kits...
Huh?
Do you know about plastic model kits?
The ones you put together.
Oh, yeah. Like those robots and boats?
Exactly.
I like to build model kits.
But recently, I bought an
expensive one, and... well...
Ah.
And now I have to cut back my food budget.
I'm a failure as a working adult, huh?
Whether you're a child or a working adult,
it's not a bad thing to indulge
in the things you enjoy.
But you shouldn't let it
negatively affect your health.
Right. I'll be careful from now on.
My bad...
I'll also hold off on pulling
all-nighters on new game release days.
I'll try!
- Let's practice the game more after we eat.
- Yes, ma'am.
Yes! First place!
I'm finally used to the mobile controls.
I'll collect more gems like this,
and unlock character scenarios—
But first, some food.
I totally forgot to eat.
I've got eggs.
I'm out of udon!
Oh, that's right. I ate that yesterday.
Hmm...
BOOM! VEGGIES
Veggies, check.
I really need to do better myself
before nagging my junior.
But cooking is so...
Let's eat.
Oh, I know.
I can read the main scenario while I eat.
Racing Girls!
I ended up staying up late playing games.
But now I can answer any questions
Kamegawa might throw at me!
Let's see here...
When I started out, I also had a lot to learn. But...
Kanna.
Tell me ASAP if you need help.
O-Okay.
Kanzaki-senpai reached out to me so that
it'd be easier for me to ask questions.
- Kamegawa.
- Yes?
If you have questions, ask me immediately.
Leaving them unanswered is
the worst thing you can do.
Thank you so much.
C'mon! Hit me, Kamegawa!
But I think I'll be okay!
What?!
I appreciate you checking in on me, Senpai.
S-Sure. Okay, then.
There's no need to hesitate.
If you don't understand something, let me know.
Thank you very much.
- Everything's good?
- Yes, ma'am!
Oh, okay.
He's not asking me anything...
It's his first proposal.
I thought he'd struggle with it a bit. Maybe...
I created an atmosphere that made it
harder for him to ask questions?
Or should I have opened up
more during lunch yesterday?
Okay.
I'll invite Kamegawa to lunch again today!
I gotta show him that I can be
a senpai he can feel at ease with!
And make sure he eats a lot!
I need to provide that safe space!
You have to join us for
lunch today, Kamegawa-kun!
Thank you. Oh, then let's
invite Kannawa-senpai, too.
Nah, Kannawa-san won't come.
She says she prefers to eat alone.
She never comes to our
drinking parties, either.
And she rarely shows up to our
New Year's and year-end parties.
Really?
Well, then, let's go! I'll show you
the good, cheap places around here.
Okay.
My chance to make a comeback...
Well, Kamegawa is brilliant.
Guess there's nothing else
for me to teach him...
What if he thinks all the stuff
I taught him is useless?!
Here you go.
It's true that I haven't been able
to show him my good side, but...
RACING GIRLS CYBER DELTA FRONTIER
Hello, this is Kannawa.
Did you eat your fill?
- I did.
- I'm glad.
I feel sleepy now...
Yes, that sounds good to me.
Yes.
In regard to that, we can discuss it
again during tomorrow's meeting...
What's wrong, Kamegawa-kun?
Sorry, be right there!
Are you planning to stay late?
Yes. I wanted to polish it up some more.
If you think it'll take a while, I can help—
No, I'll be okay!
Y-You're not being modest, are you?
You're sure you don't need my help?
Thank you, but I've got it handled.
I-I see.
Good work.
Good work today!
Kamegawa said he'd be okay...
And there's probably
nothing more I can teach him...
But there's no way I can go home
and leave a newbie to work overtime!
Sneak...
Um, Senpai? I thought you went home?
He caught me...
I-I just remembered that I had
a little more work to do, too.
Is that so?
PLEASE WAIT...
Wh-What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, the last trains will leave soon.
Time to head home!
No, I'm almost finished.
Please go on without me, Senpai.
- Actually, I'll stay, too—
- You know...
When I read your proposals, I was moved.
Huh?
They were easy to follow,
and so carefully written...
I could tell you really wanted to
convey what makes the game fun.
You're always so busy,
and the others rely on you so much.
I decided I didn't want to present
something half-hearted to you,
and end up wasting your time.
Huh?
Wait, huh?! What's wrong, Senpai?
Oh... My eyes are a bit dry.
- Here, have some tissues!
- Thanks.
It's good that you're giving it your all.
But if you push yourself too hard,
you'll cause trouble for those around you.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Even I wasn't able to do everything
well right from the start.
In fact, I think... you're managing
far better than I ever did.
Thank you for being so considerate...
Even for lunch.
You prefer to eat alone, and yet
you went out of your way to invite me.
N-No, I...
I invited you because
I wanted to eat with you!
Wait, what am I saying?!
Thank you so much, Senpai.
- Now hurry up and finish it!
- Yes, ma'am!
RETRIEVING A VEHICLE FOR YOU.
CANCEL - REGULAR TAXI - NEXT
YOUR VEHICLE IS ON THE WAY. ETA - CANCEL - NEXT
Kamegawa, the taxi will be here in ten—
You did good.
There!